Good morning.
It's probably about 6:15 right now.
I'm here.
Can you see me?
I just landed at Kanada Airport.
Today, I'm going to challenge myself to see how many planes I can take in one day.
Hokkaido in the north
Hokkaido in the north and Kyushu in the south.
I'd like to go there in a day.
Let's go for it!
Ooh!
Oh!
First of all, I'm going to get on the first flight in the morning.
Off I go!
First of all, we're here at Matsuyama Airport.
Ehime.
Wow!
I got on a Boeing 737!
I can only stay here for less than an hour
I have less than an hour to stay here.
I'm going to enjoy it!
It's amazing!
It's like a tondo glass window.
And here it's like this.
Funny.
Lilyn.
That's amazing.
It's so beautiful.
It's my first time here.
Wow.
Wow!
Tangerine juice from the faucet!
I think I'll have some tangerine juice for now!
One tangerine juice from the faucet, please.
I wonder if I can see it from the faucet.
I got it!
Tangerine juice from the tap.
I'm so happy!
Bon appétit!
Yum!
Too delicious!
Delicious!
Wow, Sky Lounge.
The Sky Lounge.
I found it.
Eh, let's go there.
Eh, eh, this way, I guess.
There's a rattlesnake.
Rumble, rattle, rattle, rattle, rattle, rattle, rattle, rattle, rattle.
I have to see the rattle, rattle, rattle.
It's on YouTube.
There's that rumble rumble rumble.
I thought, "I wish I could have been there.
Look at this.
Griggler.
Oh, really?
I want to buy it so bad.
It says it's the only one in the Sky Lounge.
Excuse me.
It's hard, isn't it?
You have a hard time?
Yeah, I know what you mean.
What is this?
Is this really right?
What do you call it?
Two, one.
It's fun.
It's printing now.
It's not coming out.
I can't get it to come out.
I'm waiting for it to come out.
I think I'll do the Akoyasinju gacha.
Okay.
I think I'll do the akoyasinju gacha.
Oh, it looks fun.
Look at this, this, this.
Akoyasinju gacha
Push.
I wonder what's going to come out
Oh!
There it is!
It's so impossible!
Wow, what's that?
It's peering.
I can't lift it.
Ew.
I can't raise it.
What's with the blue and white
Earrings.
I could wear them.
They're so cute!
I'm glad I did it.
Thank you so much.
I got it! It's here!
It's here.
This is bad.
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
It's so funny!
Ha-ha-ha-haHa-ha-ha-ha!
what is this?
This is so funny!
Celebrate Springtime
It's outside the Harajuku deck.
Maybe I should go there.
It's a big deck.
Wow.
Wow!
It's really nice.
Wow, it's so cool!
There's a prop plane.
I think this is the one that rides... the moon.
Wow!
It's landing.
Go home.
They're filming before they land.
All right.
It's, uh, cold. Let's go in.
It's cold.
I wasn't planning on going outside today.
I didn't bring a coat.
It's too cold.
I think I'll go on the next plane
Jaco-Katsu
Ew.
Here's your $150 back.
Thank you
Bon appétit.
Thank you very much.
Wow!
All right. - All right.
Good.
What are you going to eat, boy? What are you going to eat, Okun?
Okun, what are you going to eat? ★
I've always wanted to come.
I'm often in Haneda.
I've never been to Haneda.
I only know the names of airports I've never been to.
So whenever I hear the name "Matsuyama Airport
I always wanted to go there.
It was the first flight in the morning, so I was anxious to see if the shops would be open.
I was worried about whether the stores would be open or not.
I had a lot of fun!
It was great!
Thank you for the food!
Ta-da!
We've just arrived at Itami Airport in Osaka!
You can see behind me...
This is...
It's a 787.
His health is not so good today.
Maybe he'll go over there and come back.
And maybe he's going to go over there and come back.
Or he may have to come back to Haneda.
I don't know yet, but I'd like to get on the plane.
I'm going to get on the plane for now.
I'm off!
I'll be waiting for you.
I'll be waiting.
Okay.
So we've arrived at New Chitose Airport.
We have arrived at New Chitose Airport
We're running now.
We arrived a little late.
I'll do my best.
There it is!
Look forward to seeing you next time!
Shut up.
Tiger.
Well, I'm off to go fishing.
See you on the shortcut.
Okay, I'm going fishing.
Enjoy.
Well, so I'm back at Fuji Haneda from New Chitose.
I came back to Fuji Haneda from New Chitose.
I'm going to take a plane again from here.
This is my fifth time to fly.
I'm sure I'll have fun.
I'm going to enjoy it.
I'm off.
That's it!
So now I'm here.
I'm in Kagoshima prefecture.
Wow!
I've been wanting to come to Kagoshima Airport
I finally made it here!
I'm so happy!
It's about 7:00 p.m.
I think it's around 7:00 p.m.
I've been flying all day!
Here we are at the airport for the last time!
First of all, I want to go to the footbath
I'm going to the footbath!
I've been sitting for a long time
Blood circulation is bad
So I'm going to soak my feet in the hot spring
I think I'll take a rest.
Take off your socks.
Okay, that feels really good.Okay, it looks so good.
I'm outside, but it's there.
They're calling it a natural wind-swept stream.
I'm gonna use it as a photo camera.
Oh, I'm so happy!
I think I'll just relax a little bit, just a little bit, and then I'll go home.
Okay.
I think I'm going to get something to eat.
I'd like to go to the deck when it's still open
Well, goodbye to Asheu for now.
Bye bye.
We're done with our ashtow.
I'm going to look for a deck now.
I'm going to look for a deck.
Ta-da!
Kojima Airport
Wow, what a surprise!
There's an exhibition.
Wow, this is amazing!
Wow!
The history of the past
Oh, my gosh!
There are so many airplanes!
Wow!
Wow.
Around here...
Is it a fighter plane?
Is that a fighter plane?
Oh, this way.
Deep.
Uh, there's also a 380.
A Beluga?
They've got a Beluga on display. Wow.
Look, a YS-11.
It's one of the planes I'd like to see.
Oh, wow.
It's fun.
What? Wait, look.
There's a mock-up.
What do you mean?
What?
Isn't it bad? There's a Mork-Up.
Are you kidding me? How is that possible?
Uh...
Excuse me.
Oh, isn't that great?
Mooked up...
I can't go!
You can't go!
Isn't it great?
Wow, that's impressive!
Is this for training?
Oh, my God!
They say you can sit here anytime you want.
I think I'll sit here.
Oh, my God!
Is this the cabin? This is a cabin. Isn't it amazing?
It's in a place where anyone can come in. Isn't it amazing?
This is awesome. I'm so excited.
It's really amazing. I'm impressed.
I thought they only had them on air force ships. It's at the airport. They have mog-ats. I'm so surprised.
I think I can get out.
What? It's so big.
This is Kagoshima.
Oh, it's so much fun!
Kagoshima airport is awesome!
You should come here!
Eh, is it famous?
It is famous among airplane fans.
Maybe I should take off my mask because there's no one here!
Ha! Comfortable.
Airplane
Airplanes here too!
If you like airplanes, or if you are a parent with a child who likes airplanes, you should definitely come here.
You can spend a whole day just at Kuboshima Airport. It's so much fun.
I don't know. Standby?
Oh, I'm on the air.
Yes, I am.
I live in Kagoshima without running Kagoshima airport.
I have to go back to Haneda Airport at the end.
We won't go back if we are hungry.
All right.
Kitchen Satsuma!
I'm going to Kitchen Satsuma!
One hamburger set and one hamburger set.
The hamburger set has two sauces, Japanese sauce and Western sauce.
Japanese, please.
Yes, ma'am.
Thank you very much.
Looks too good.
Josie.
So much breadcrumbs.
Okay, here we go.
Cuts.
Yum!
That's great!
We'll go back to the ship after this.
We're going back to Kansai.
Pork cutlet!Cutlets.
Here, don't you want some?
Delicious!
So here we are, back at Haneda Airport Terminal 1.
Today, I have traveled around the country by air a total of six times.
I hope I have conveyed the quality of each airport to you, and I had a lot of fun myself.
I hope that I was able to convey to you the good qualities of each airport, and since I enjoyed myself so much, I would like to visit each airport again at my leisure.
I would like to take my time to visit each airport again, and I would like to visit other airports as well.
I hope you enjoyed it as much as I did.
Please visit airports around Japan!
Thank you very much, bye-bye!